Sapphire Praxical LLC Privacy Policy

This document was last updated on December 4th, 2017 7:00pm EST

This Privacy Policy discusses the manner in which Sapphire.moe collects, uses, maintains and discloses any information from users of Sapphire.moe.

Personal identification information
-----------------------------------

Our web server doesn't log IP addresses for accesses on the server. IP addresses are only logged for the error log for debugging and deleted after 3 days. However Cloudflare blocks almost all IP addresses to the server so most of these IPs are just Cloudflare's IPs.

Non-personal identification information
---------------------------------------

Non-personal identification information may include the browser type and the OS in error logs. This info only lasts 3 days.

Cookies
-------

Visiting Sapphire may generate a cookie in your browser. It's from Cloudflare. We don't currently use cookies besides that.

How we use collected information
--------------------------------

Access and error logs from nginx are used to troubleshoot issues with the server and identify if we are under attack or being abused by a botnet.

How we protect your information
-------------------------------

HTTPS encryption on all pages, Error log IP addresses deleted after 3 days, no stored usernames or passwords.

Sharing your personal information
---------------------------------

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.

Third party websites
--------------------

We have linked, on the website, links to Twitter, GitGud, and Opengem.org for information links.

Changes to this privacy policy
------------------------------

Sapphire.moe has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our site. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms
------------------------------

By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us via: admin at opengem dot org.

#### Sapphire

#### Resources

#### Company
